M FAJAR NUGROHO ALAM A.Md.T

Bandung Barat (Kab.) 40288 | linkedin.com/in/muhammad-fajar-nugroho-alam-654311200/| +6281388669869 | invasionfajar@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Backend web and mobile application with experience in research and work, have experience in React JS framework, React Native, PHP, Laravel Interested in all related to Javascript Programs, Laravel Programs and Database Provisioning. Interested in new things that can help develop Websites and mobile applications so that they can create programs that are structured and easy to use by users. always participate in competitions and get several awards such as: Finalist Gemastik 2021, Best of 5 Innovillage 2020 and PKM 2021.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Bandung Techno Park

(June 2020 - July 2020)

Back End Developer

- As front end developers collaborate with frontend developers to make websites more responsive using the lumen framework
- Create ERD Database
- Provide reports and post progress on git/github

Docotel (January 2021 - July 2021)

Back End Developer

- Help work on features and bugs on the system using the YII 2 framework.
- Adding some features to the system via API and testing using postman
- Progress report with scrum method every working day

EDUCATION

Telkom University, Bandung

Associate Diploma of Telecommunication Technology

(August 2018 - September 2021) 3.54/4.00

Relevant Coursework:

- PHPprogramming,
- Javascript programming,
- Internet of Things
- Laravel Framework.
- Honors: -Cum Laude with honors Alerty monitoring disaster using React-Native and Firebase

- Awards: Finalist Gemastik (Pergelaran Mahasiswa TIK) Puspernas 2021
 - PKM 2021 PIMNAS
 - Best of 5 Anugrah Innovillage 2020 Telkom University
- Activities and Societies:
 - -Programming Practicum Assistant (TELNET),
 - -AssistantLecturer for Programming Practicum II,
 - -Assistant Practicum Design Communication Visual

SELECTED PROJECT

1. Yii Ekspedisi Master (YII 2 Framework)

https://github.com/mfajarna/yii-ekspedisi-master

2. Laravel Telegram (Laravel Framewok)

https://github.com/mfajarna/laravel-telegram

3. Web Monitoring Al-Azhar (JS + Firebase)

https://github.com/mfajarna/WebMonitoring-AlAzhar

4. Monitoring Tandon Mobile App (React Native Framework)

https://github.com/mfajarna/RN-MonitoringTandon

5. Hasnida Collection Mobile Apps (React Native Framework)

https://github.com/mfajarna/hasnidacollection

7. Hasnida Collection Back-End (Laravel Framework)

https://github.com/mfajarna/hasnidacollection-backend

8. Hasnida Collection Admin (React Native Framework)

https://github.com/mfajarna/hasnidacollection-admin

9 NPK Mobile Apps (React Native Framework)

https://github.com/mfajarna/NPK

10. E-Tocologist (React Native Framework)

https://github.com/mfajarna/etocologist

11. E-Tocologist Back-End (Laravel Framework)

https://github.com/mfajarna/etocologist-backend

12. Alerty Website Monitoring (Firebase + JS)

https://github.com/mfajarna/alerty-web-monitoring

13. Alerty Mobile Apps (React Native Framework)

https://github.com/mfajarna/Alerty

14. Pulse Oximetri Mobile Apps (React Native Framework)

https://github.com/mfajarna/bluetooth-detect

15. SunSky Mobile Apps (React Native Framework)

https://github.com/mfajarna/SunSky-Gaming-Shop

16. Smartcanteen Back End (Laravel Framework)

https://github.com/mfajarna/smartcanteen-backend

17. Web TopUp Games (Laravel Framework)

SKILL

React JS (Junior), React Native (Intermediate), EcmaScript, Javascript (Intermediate), Bootstrap 5, HTML, SCSS, Git/Github, PHP (Intermediate), Laravel Framework (Intermediate), UI Design Figma (Intermediate), Trello, English (Intermediate), Native Indonesia.